export const marvelQuestions = [
  {
    question: "What is Captain America's real name?",
    option1: "Steve Rogers",
    option2: "Tony Stark",
    option3: "Bruce Banner",
    option4: "Clint Barton",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which infinity stone was hidden on Vormir?",
    option1: "Mind Stone",
    option2: "Soul Stone",
    option3: "Reality Stone",
    option4: "Power Stone",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Thor's hammer?",
    option1: "Stormbreaker",
    option2: "Mjolnir",
    option3: "Gungnir",
    option4: "Excalibur",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who created Ultron?",
    option1: "Tony Stark & Bruce Banner",
    option2: "Hank Pym",
    option3: "Thor",
    option4: "Nick Fury",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which actor plays Spider-Man in the MCU?",
    option1: "Tobey Maguire",
    option2: "Andrew Garfield",
    option3: "Tom Holland",
    option4: "Chris Evans",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is Black Panther’s real name?",
    option1: "T'Challa",
    option2: "Shuri",
    option3: "Okoye",
    option4: "M'Baku",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Which Avenger is known as the ‘strongest Avenger’?",
    option1: "Hulk",
    option2: "Thor",
    option3: "Doctor Strange",
    option4: "Captain Marvel",
    ans: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the villain in Avengers: Infinity War?",
    option1: "Loki",
    option2: "Ultron",
    option3: "Thanos",
    option4: "Red Skull",
    ans: 3,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of Iron Man’s AI assistant?",
    option1: "J.A.R.V.I.S.",
    option2: "F.R.I.D.A.Y.",
    option3: "Edith",
    option4: "Karen",
    ans: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the King of Asgard at the end of Avengers: Endgame?",
    option1: "Loki",
    option2: "Thor",
    option3: "Odin",
    option4: "Valkyrie",
    ans: 4,
  },
];
